<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Nick D Blog</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nick D Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nickdnickd.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Health Insurance Transparency</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2022-11-20-heath-insurance-transparency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2022-11-20-heath-insurance-transparency/</guid><description>A Song of Charge Books and Actuaries Insurance is a simple question with a complicated answer. How can an insurance company pay the minimal amount while still retaining employers as customers. Hospitals (and the providers that compose them) have a similar question: how can I charge the most that insurance companies and patients will actually pay. This battle happens on the other side of the curtain. They know virtually nothing until they receive their bill submitted through insurance.</description></item><item><title>IRS v BTC</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2021-3-1-crypto-taxes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2021-3-1-crypto-taxes/</guid><description>UPDATE TurboTax has now pulled Coinbase from the list of providers for CSV uploading. While less confusing, the workaround I created no longer allows us to &amp;ldquo;spoof&amp;rdquo; a proper CSV. You can still use the output from this blog to enter into TurboTax&amp;hellip; but unfortunately it&amp;rsquo;s gotta be manual.
Crypto grows up This year in TurboTax, the paywall maze willed into existance by lobbying, a question will pop up asking if you&amp;rsquo;ve sold or received cryptocurrency in 2020.</description></item><item><title>Asynchronous Uploads</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2020-11-1-async-uploads/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2020-11-1-async-uploads/</guid><description>I will never forget the first time I killed the music in a local coffee shop. Struggling to teach myself &amp;ldquo;machine learning&amp;rdquo;, I decided to download large dataset from the internet. As is typical with these types of workloads, the download size was well over 100 GB. When I clicked download, Google Drive split the file into several chunks available to download simultaneously.
The competing music streaming device yeilded immediately, and acoustic pop covers were replaced with 4'33&amp;quot; on repeat until I realized what I&amp;rsquo;d done.</description></item><item><title>Avoiding Manual Data Entry</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2020-09-12-avoiding-manual-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2020-09-12-avoiding-manual-data/</guid><description>Interview Season Doctors have it rough. After graduating medical school, they enter a period of indentured servitude known as residency. It is not uncommon to hear of over 80 hour weeks, 12 hour shifts and DOMA&amp;rsquo;s. DOMA stands for &amp;ldquo;Day Off, My Ass&amp;rdquo; which describes the period of time between a night shift, letting out at 7am, and a day shift starting at 7am. Technically 24 hours, but most of it is spent asleep.</description></item><item><title>Let There Be Sound</title><link>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2018-01-16-let-there-be-sound/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nickdnickd.com/posts/2018-01-16-let-there-be-sound/</guid><description>Beautiful Soup Does it bother anyone else to think about how we can&amp;rsquo;t completely describe complicated things? Most of us have heard of the Uncertainty principle describing that a more accurate measurement of position of a particle sacrifies the momentum accuracy. Here breadth, by principle, is sacrificed for depth. On a larger scale, we probably do not have enough compute on planet earth to describe a cold front, let alone weather, in a way that yeilds complete confidence in weather reports.</description></item></channel></rss>